{
  "worksheet": [
    {
      "number": 1,
      "question": "4 + 3",
      "skill_code": "1A",
      "options": [
        "9",
        "8",
        "6",
        "7"
      ],
      "correct_answer_index": 3,
      "possible_distractors": [
        "8",
        "9",
        "5",
        "6"
      ]
    },
    {
      "number": 2,
      "question": "1 + 7",
      "skill_code": "1A",
      "options": [
        "9",
        "7",
        "6",
        "8"
      ],
      "correct_answer_index": 3,
      "possible_distractors": [
        "9",
        "10",
        "6",
        "7"
      ]
    },
    {
      "number": 3,
      "question": "3 + 0",
      "skill_code": "1A",
      "options": [
        "5",
        "1",
        "2",
        "3"
      ],
      "correct_answer_index": 3,
      "possible_distractors": [
        "1",
        "2",
        "4",
        "5"
      ]
    },
    {
      "number": 4,
      "question": "1 - 1",
      "skill_code": "1S",
      "options": [
        "1",
        "0",
        "2",
        "-1"
      ],
      "correct_answer_index": 1,
      "possible_distractors": [
        "1",
        "2",
        "-1",
        "-2"
      ]
    },
    {
      "number": 5,
      "question": "8 - 0",
      "skill_code": "1S",
      "options": [
        "7",
        "8",
        "9",
        "10"
      ],
      "correct_answer_index": 1,
      "possible_distractors": [
        "9",
        "10",
        "6",
        "7"
      ]
    },
    {
      "number": 6,
      "question": "83 + 3",
      "skill_code": "2A1",
      "options": [
        "113",
        "87",
        "86",
        "85"
      ],
      "correct_answer_index": 2,
      "possible_distractors": [
        "113",
        "85",
        "87"
      ]
    },
    {
      "number": 7,
      "question": "54 + 4",
      "skill_code": "2A1",
      "options": [
        "94",
        "59",
        "57",
        "58"
      ],
      "correct_answer_index": 3,
      "possible_distractors": [
        "57",
        "59",
        "94"
      ]
    },
    {
      "number": 8,
      "question": "78 + 0",
      "skill_code": "2A1",
      "options": [
        "78",
        "78",
        "77",
        "79"
      ],
      "correct_answer_index": 0,
      "possible_distractors": [
        "77",
        "78",
        "79"
      ]
    },
    {
      "number": 9,
      "question": "29 + 60",
      "skill_code": "2A2",
      "options": [
        "79",
        "99",
        "88",
        "89"
      ],
      "correct_answer_index": 3,
      "possible_distractors": [
        "88",
        "99",
        "79"
      ]
    },
    {
      "number": 10,
      "question": "87 + 61",
      "skill_code": "2A2",
      "options": [
        "158",
        "148",
        "48",
        "138"
      ],
      "correct_answer_index": 1,
      "possible_distractors": [
        "138",
        "48",
        "147",
        "149",
        "248",
        "158"
      ]
    },
    {
      "number": 11,
      "question": "31 - 0",
      "skill_code": "2S1",
      "options": [
        "30",
        "32",
        "31",
        "31"
      ],
      "correct_answer_index": 2,
      "possible_distractors": [
        "32",
        "30",
        "31"
      ]
    },
    {
      "number": 12,
      "question": "74 - 0",
      "skill_code": "2S1",
      "options": [
        "74",
        "75",
        "73",
        "74"
      ],
      "correct_answer_index": 0,
      "possible_distractors": [
        "73",
        "74",
        "75"
      ]
    },
    {
      "number": 13,
      "question": "34 - 20",
      "skill_code": "2S2",
      "options": [
        "15",
        "13",
        "14",
        "24"
      ],
      "correct_answer_index": 2,
      "possible_distractors": [
        "4",
        "13",
        "15",
        "54",
        "24"
      ]
    },
    {
      "number": 14,
      "question": "15 - 13",
      "skill_code": "2S2",
      "options": [
        "28",
        "3",
        "2",
        "1"
      ],
      "correct_answer_index": 2,
      "possible_distractors": [
        "1",
        "3",
        "28"
      ]
    },
    {
      "number": 15,
      "question": "6 \u00d7 5",
      "skill_code": "T5",
      "options": [
        "24",
        "30",
        "18",
        "42"
      ],
      "correct_answer_index": 1,
      "possible_distractors": [
        "24",
        "42",
        "18",
        "36"
      ]
    },
    {
      "number": 16,
      "question": "8 \u00d7 1",
      "skill_code": "T5",
      "options": [
        "0",
        "16",
        "8",
        "24"
      ],
      "correct_answer_index": 2,
      "possible_distractors": [
        "24",
        "16",
        "0"
      ]
    },
    {
      "number": 17,
      "question": "6 \u00d7 3",
      "skill_code": "T10",
      "options": [
        "30",
        "6",
        "18",
        "12"
      ],
      "correct_answer_index": 2,
      "possible_distractors": [
        "24",
        "12",
        "6",
        "30"
      ]
    },
    {
      "number": 18,
      "question": "722 + 155",
      "skill_code": "3A",
      "options": [
        "877",
        "876",
        "977",
        "878"
      ],
      "correct_answer_index": 0,
      "possible_distractors": [
        "867",
        "777",
        "876",
        "878",
        "977",
        "887"
      ]
    },
    {
      "number": 19,
      "question": "319 - 212",
      "skill_code": "3S",
      "options": [
        "107",
        "108",
        "106",
        "117"
      ],
      "correct_answer_index": 0,
      "possible_distractors": [
        "7",
        "106",
        "108",
        "207",
        "531",
        "117"
      ]
    },
    {
      "number": 20,
      "question": "21 \u00d7 3",
      "skill_code": "2M1",
      "options": [
        "62",
        "24",
        "63",
        "64"
      ],
      "correct_answer_index": 2,
      "possible_distractors": [
        "24",
        "64",
        "62"
      ]
    }
  ],
  "answer_key": [
    {
      "question_number": 1,
      "correct_option": "D",
      "correct_answer": 7
    },
    {
      "question_number": 2,
      "correct_option": "D",
      "correct_answer": 8
    },
    {
      "question_number": 3,
      "correct_option": "D",
      "correct_answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question_number": 4,
      "correct_option": "B",
      "correct_answer": 0
    },
    {
      "question_number": 5,
      "correct_option": "B",
      "correct_answer": 8
    },
    {
      "question_number": 6,
      "correct_option": "C",
      "correct_answer": 86
    },
    {
      "question_number": 7,
      "correct_option": "D",
      "correct_answer": 58
    },
    {
      "question_number": 8,
      "correct_option": "A",
      "correct_answer": 78
    },
    {
      "question_number": 9,
      "correct_option": "D",
      "correct_answer": 89
    },
    {
      "question_number": 10,
      "correct_option": "B",
      "correct_answer": 148
    },
    {
      "question_number": 11,
      "correct_option": "C",
      "correct_answer": 31
    },
    {
      "question_number": 12,
      "correct_option": "A",
      "correct_answer": 74
    },
    {
      "question_number": 13,
      "correct_option": "C",
      "correct_answer": 14
    },
    {
      "question_number": 14,
      "correct_option": "C",
      "correct_answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question_number": 15,
      "correct_option": "B",
      "correct_answer": 30
    },
    {
      "question_number": 16,
      "correct_option": "C",
      "correct_answer": 8
    },
    {
      "question_number": 17,
      "correct_option": "C",
      "correct_answer": 18
    },
    {
      "question_number": 18,
      "correct_option": "A",
      "correct_answer": 877
    },
    {
      "question_number": 19,
      "correct_option": "A",
      "correct_answer": 107
    },
    {
      "question_number": 20,
      "correct_option": "C",
      "correct_answer": 63
    }
  ],
  "total_questions": 20
}